Guide to the Yale College Student Declamations
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale College student declamations
1755-1793
RU 145
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.75
The records consist of Yale student declamations.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 47 (YRG 47), Collections documenting teaching and learning in Yale academic programs.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of Yale student declamations.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by language and date.
Recitations; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Students
- Declamations, Series I
  - Class of 1787, 1784-1787 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 4)
  - Latin Declamations
    - 1755-1759 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1760-1764 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1765, 1767-1770 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1772-1778, 1781-1783 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Greek and Latin Declamations
    - 1784 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 1785 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 1786-1787, 1789-1791, 1793 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Latin Declamations, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)